Dairon Reijna

Swindon, Wiltshire • 07951092464 • dairon.reijna@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/dairon-reijna

Objective:

Highly analytical and strategic Project Officer with over 13 years of public sector experience, adept at driving change, new initiatives, and strategy delivery, with a keen interest in the skills and employment support system. Bringing a track record of successful project lifecycle management, stakeholder engagement, compliance, and service delivery. Completed MBA with merit and Prince 2 certified, equipped with excellent communication, empathy, and collaboration skills vital to project management roles.

Core Skills:

- Project Lifecycle Management
- Stakeholder Engagement and Management
- Compliance and Regulations Tracking
- Service Delivery and Budget Monitoring
- Business Case Development and Implementation
- Financial and Commissioning Support
- Data Analysis and Reporting
- Business Plans and Strategy Execution
- Effective Governance and Change Management

Work Experience:

Swindon Borough Council • Full-time • 03/2023 - Present SEND Finance

- Led business change projects to optimise SEN commissioning finance, resulting in improved payment processing and increased efficiency.
- Provided financial and commissioning support to senior management, ensuring effective budget allocation and resource utilisation.
- Coordinated place planning for SEN, maintaining an overview of specialist provision placements to inform commissioning decisions.
- Monitored and reported on a £6 million budget, ensuring compliance with financial regulations and policies.

Slough Children Services • Full-time • 01/2017 - 09/2022 Service Manager

- Prepared reports on policy, regulations, and service performance, contributing to improved departmental performance.
- Led a collaborative team of 5 staff, solving problems and driving positive outcomes.
- Executed business plans and strategies, ensuring smooth operations and service delivery.
- Tracked compliance with regulations and policies related to customer health needs.

Achievements:

- Delivered 150% increase in stakeholder engagement over 6 months, exceeding goals and transforming outcomes for client-focused organisation.
- Evaluated and analysed budget spend, contracted new suppliers, and implemented digital invoicing, resulting in a savings of 18% and prompt payment of 72% of invoices.
- Awarded "A Star of the Year" and "A Star Award" in 2017 for exceptional work ethic, contributions, and dedication to the organisation.

Social & Health Insurances • Sint Maarten • Full-time • 10/2014 - 12/2016 Finance Officer

- Appointed as finance rep during construction of office buildings for commercial hire.
- Served as the main contact for inbound workflows from key stakeholders, ensuring quality and efficient processing.
- Implemented automated payment processes, resulting in increased efficiency and reduced processing time.
- Managed debtor and creditor responsibilities, overseeing payment transactions.
- Maintained stakeholder engagement with the Tax and Customs Administration.

Achievements:

• Improved payment processing through the implementation of automated BACS payments, reducing year-end processes from 3 to 1 month, a 67% increase in efficiency.

Volunteer Experience:

- Mentor for at-risk Youth GIFTED Foundation St. Maarten positive entertainment & youth development
- Board Member iDad Foundation St. Maarten challenging fathers to step up and be active
- Project Planner Youth2Xtreme Foundation St. Maarten Impactful events for Caribbean youth.

Education & Training:

Master in Business Administration

Oxford Brookes University • Oxford • GPA: Merit • 03/2019 - 09/2022

Prince 2 Project Management

Axelos • 09/2021